Daniel Sancho will try to avoid the
Daniel Sancho tratará de evitar el
Bangkok Hilton where
Bangkok Hilton donde se mezclan asesinos
serial killers and drug dealers mingle, he will be charged with
en serie y traficantes se le jugará por
premeditated murder and if he is
asesinato premeditado y en caso de ser
sentenced to the maximum possible sentence he will
condenado a la máxima pena posible
end up on death row. The
acabará en el corredor de la muerte el
menu is that they have said it is for passive
menú que sí lo han dicho por pasiva
premeditated crime here it is the
crimen premeditado aquí es pena de
death penalty. I think they are saying all the
muerte yo creo que van diciendo todo el
time that later it won't be because they say that he does
tiempo que luego no sea porque dicen que
confess and such. Well, maybe they will give him a
sí confiesa y tal Pues igual y se lo
life sentence but
hacen como cadena perpetua pero crimen
premeditated crime death sentence
premeditado cadena de muerte pena de
death penalty. The other day they were saying that
muerte el otro día estaban diciendo que
if he confessed in court, it was
si en el juicio confesaba como que era
a clear mitigating factor to collaborate with the
un atenuante claro colaborar con la
police, confess, help solve the
policía confesar ayudar a desvelar el
crime, all that before, of course, cooperating with
crimen todo eso antes claro cooperar con
the police is a mitigating factor and you get a
la policía es un atenuante y te cae
lesser sentence there and you get a lesser sentence here, of
menos pena allí y te cae menos pena aquí
course, it is not blackmail, it is cooperation and
claro no es un chantaje es cooperación y
for cooperating in the United States there are also
por cooperar en Estados Unidos también
many states the capital punishment and
existen muchos estados la pena capital y
if you cooperate you plead guilty and such, they
si cooperas te declaras culpable y tal
also reduce your life sentence.
también te rebajan la cadena perpetua O
So that is not blackmail, that is
sea que eso no es un chantaje eso se
done in all countries.
hacen todos los países del